JAN ONDRICH MSc

Summary

Jan is an experienced professional in the infrastructure sector with specific expertise in the energy industry. Jan combines in-depth techno-economic knowledge with comprehensive understanding of market structures, trends, investment, and trading options. Over the past 15 years Jan has worked with senior management of institutional investors as well as strategic investors sourcing investment opportunities, creating business plans and presenting opportunities to senior management/investment committees.

Jan leads investment and asset management part of Amper Group where he focuses on origination and management of investment opportunities in renewable power generation and power grid services sectors. Earlier in his career Jan has advised large institutional investors on investments into infrastructure, such as combined power and heat generation as well as on energy efficiency and renewable energy opportunities. Jan has led or supported projects for Europe's major utilities, advising on institutional development, strategies, policies, regulation, market development and financing.

Jan is a graduate of London School of Economics (MSc in European Policy and Governance, 2005) and represents the City of Prague on supervisory board of Pražská Energetika Holding.

Jan acts as a board member responsible for finance of a charity Act for Others which supports handicapped children in the Czech Republic.

Jan is a Czech national fluent in verbal and written English and has working knowledge of German.

Core Skills and Experience

- 15 years' experience of leading numerous cross-country management consulting projects across Europe for Europe's largest utilities and institutional investors.
- Managing all aspects of business including fundraising, project origination, execution and delivery, client and investor relationships and staff management.
- Originated and co-developed renewable and thermal power generation projects with utilities.
- · Managing advisors such as technical, legal and financial due-diligence providers.
- Preparation of materials for Investment Committees, including detailed market/commercial reports and financial models.
- Negotiation of terms sheets of key agreements, such as Power Purchase Agreements, heat offtake contracts, tolling agreements, EPC and O&M.
- Detailed understanding of power, gas and carbon markets with specific focus on short-term and balancing/ancillary services markets.
- Detailed understanding of economics of co-generation projects.
- Developed and modelled dispatch concept of dynamic district heating strategy utilising flexible generators to service balancing and intraday markets.
- · Author of numerous feasibility and market assessment studies for strategic as well as financial investors.
- Experienced analyst with excellent quantitative and qualitative analytical skills, including advanced statistical modelling.

Employment Summary

Investment origination and asset management 2020-present

Amper Asset Management

Prague, Czech Republic Co-Founder and Managing Director

- Responsible for project origination and execution.
- Develops and executes funding strategies.
- · Sources equity and debt financing.
- Focus on renewable and "new energy" projects such as grid infrastructure and decentralized systems.

Electricity distribution and sales 2019 - present

Pražská Energetika Holding

Prague, Czech Republic Member of the Supervisory Board

- · Representing interests of the City of Prague.
- · Focus on regulation and markets.

Project Development 2015 - 2020

SWG Strom & Wärme GmbH

Berlin, Germany

Founder and Managing Director

- Responsible for project origination and management, HR, and financing.
- Co-develops market and plant operating strategies.
- Responsible for market analysis, product development and fund-raising activities.
- Manages and coordinates analytical, legal and consulting teams supporting SWG project development team.
- · Manages client, investor and supplier relationships.

Private Equity / Structured Finance 2015 - 2018

EnerCap Capital Partners

Prague, Czech Republic

- Advised and supported the development of the E3F Investment strategy.
- Continued market analysis, strategy evolution and opportunity identification.
- Directing work of Enercap analysts.
- · Supports risk assessment on target projects and markets.

Management Consultancy 2007 - 2015

Candole Partners Ltd

Prague, CZ Managing Partner

- Responsible for firm management, business development and HR.
- Assembled and led teams of consultant from various countries on projects which often involved multiple countries of Central and South East Europe.
- Responsible for quality of analytical work. Originated and managed projects with leading European utilities such as E.ON, GDF Suez and Fortum in Central and South East Europe.
- · Created market entry and business strategies.

Management Consultancy 2005 - 2007

CEC Government Relations

Prague, CZ Consultant

 Advised utility clients and infrastructure investors on regulatory and policy risk in CEE and Czech Republic in particular.

Education

2004 - 2005 London School of Economics, London, UK

Master of Science European Politics and Governance

 ${\it Master's programme focused on quantitative research methods, research methodology}$

and statistics.

2000 - 2004 University of New York (Empire State College) in Prague, Prague, CZ

Bachelor of Science International and European Economic Studies

Programme focused on Microeconomics, Corporate Finance, Financial Accounting and

Statistics.

Languages: English, German, French